American Council for Emigres in the Professions; Records ger017
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP, Undated; 4; originals - 1160 individual files
  - Heichelheim, Fritz M., Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 110)
  - Heine, Fritz, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 111)
  - Heinemann, Frederick H., Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 112)
  - Heitz, Emil, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 113)
  - Helleiner, Karl, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 114)
  - Helly, Eduard, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 115)
  - Henmann, Pierre, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 116)
  - Henri-Simon, Pierre, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 117)
  - Hering, Jean, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 118)
  - Herling, Heinz-Horst, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 119)
  - Hernando, Manuel, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 120)
  - Hersch, Liebmann, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 121)
  - Hertz, Richard, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 122)
  - Herz, Paul, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 123)
  - Herzog-Haüser, Gertrud, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 124)
  - Hessberg, Richard J., Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 125)
  - Hessen, Sergius, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 126)
  - Hettner, Alfred, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 127)
  - Heumann, Albert, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 128)
  - Heyerdahl, Thor, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 129)
  - Hilferding, Rudolf, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 130)
  - Himmelschein, George, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 131)
  - Hintze, Hedwig, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 132)
  - Hirsch, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 133)
  - Hirschberg, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 134)
  - Hirschberg, Kurt, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 135)
  - Hirszfeld, Ludwig, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 136)
  - Hoch, Paul, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 137)
  - Hocquenghem, Alexis, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 138)
  - Hoeguer, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 139)
  - Hoepke, Dr, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 140)
  - Hoffer, Willy, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 141)
  - Holtgreter, J., Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 142)
  - Holweck, Fernand, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 143)
  - Honegger, Hans, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 144)
  - Honigsheim, Paul, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 145)
  - Hopf, Heinz, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 146)
  - Hosiasson-Lindenbaum, Janina, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 147)
  - Hosiosky, I., Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 148)
  - Hostelet, George, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 149)
  - Houang, Kia-tching, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 150)
  - Houtermans, Fritz, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 151)
  - Huisman, G., Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 152)
  - Hupka, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 153)
  - Husserl, Gerhardt, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 154)
  - Huth, Arno, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 155)
  - Ichheiser, Gustav, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 156)
  - Ingarden, Roman, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 157)
  - Ingebrigtsen, Ragnvald, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 158)
  - Iros, Ernst, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 159)
  - Isay, Ernst, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 160)
  - Isay, Harry, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 161)
  - Iscar, Agustin, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 1)
  - Ising, Johanna, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 2)
  - Issatschenko, Alexander, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 3)
  - Ivanoff, Nina, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 4)
  - Jacob-Loewenson, Alice, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 5)
  - Jacobsen, Lis, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 6)
  - Jacobsen, Walter, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 7)
  - Jacoby, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 8)
  - Jacoby, Albrecht, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 9)
  - Jahiel, Richard, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 10)
  - Jahoda, Leopold, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 11)
  - Jameson, Egon, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 12)
  - Jasinowski, Bogumil, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 13)
  - Jaspers, Karl, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 14)
  - Jeppesen, Knud, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 15)
  - Jimeno, Alfredo Matilia, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 16)
  - Jimeno, Aurelio Matilla, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 17)
  - Jirmounsky, Myron, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 18)
  - Jitta, A. C. Josephus, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 19)
  - Joergensen, Joergen, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 20)
  - Jokl, Norbert, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 21)
  - Joliot, Fr. and Irene Curie, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 22)
  - Jollos, Waldemar, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 23)
  - Joseph, Ludwig, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 24)
  - Jouhandeau, Marcel, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 25)
  - Joxe, Louis, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 26)
  - Juergens, Rudolf, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 27)
  - Juliusburger, Otto, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 28)
  - Juris, Kalman, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 29)
  - Kabelik, Jan, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 30)
  - Kaeber, Ernst, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 31)
  - Kagenikoff, Alexander, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 32)
  - Kaiser-Blueth, Kurt, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 33)
  - Kalbeck, Paul, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 34)
  - Kalecki, M., Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 35)
  - Kalmus, Hans, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 36)
  - Kann, Richard, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 37)
  - Kanitz, Ernst, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 38)
  - Kantorowicz, Alfred, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 39)
  - Karpinski, Martin, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 40)
  - Karsen, Fritz, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 41)
  - Kate ten, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 42)
  - Kastein, Joseph, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 43)
  - Katkov, George, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 44)
  - Katona, Kathleen and Paul, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 45)
  - Katz, David, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 46)
  - Katz, Heidi K., Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 47)
  - Katz, Leopold, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 48)
  - Katz, Peter, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 49)
  - Katz, Richard, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 50)
  - Kaufman, Rudolf, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 51)
  - Kaufmann, Erich, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 52)
  - Kaufungen, Kunz von, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 53)
  - Kaulla, Rudolf, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 54)
  - Kaunitz, Hans, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 55)
  - Kayser, Jacqes, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 56)
  - Keller, Rudolph, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 57)
  - Kempner, Walter, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 58)
  - Kessel, Franz T., Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 59)
  - Kestenberg, Leo, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 60)
  - Kheraskov, Ivan, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 61)
  - Kisch, Guido, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 62)
  - Kivillovitch, Moissaye, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 63)
  - Klanfer, Julius, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 64)
  - Klang, Heinrich, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 65)
  - Kleinlerer, David, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 66)
  - Klopfer, Bruno, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 67)
  - Knobloch, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 68)
  - Kobrak, Franz W., Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 69)
  - Kochanowsky, Boris, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 70)
  - Koenigsberger, Paul, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 71)
  - Koerber, Joseph, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 72)
  - Kohn, Herbert, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 73)
  - Kohn, Moritz, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 74)
  - Kohnstamm, Philipp Abraham, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 75)
  - Kokoszynska-Lutman, Maria, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 76)
  - Koller, Philipp Alexander, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 77)
  - Kollmann, Erich, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 78)
  - Königsfeld, Harry, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 79)
  - Koopmans, Johan G., Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 80)
  - Koral, Waclaw, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 81)
  - Kotarbinski, Tadeusz, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 82)
  - Koulicher, Alexandre, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 83)
  - Kowalow, Paul, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 84)
  - Kowalski, Jadeusz, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 85)
  - Kracauer, Siegfried, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 86)
  - Kraft, Julius, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 87)
  - Kral, Alois, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 88)
  - Kramer, Franz, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 89)
  - Kramers, Hans A., Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 90)
  - Krasner, Marc, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 91)
  - Kraus, Paul, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 92)
  - Kraus, Siegfried, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 93)
  - Krauss, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 94)
  - Krautheimer, Richard, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 95)
  - Kreilisheim, Otto, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 96)
  - Krenek, Ernst, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 97)
  - Kretschmer, Fritz, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 98)
  - Krizenecky, V., Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 99)
  - Krol, Michael, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 100)
  - Kraus, Oskar, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 101)
  - Kuczynski, Jürgen, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 102)
  - Kuehne, Otto, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 103)
  - Kuerbs, Friedrich, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 104)
  - Kuffler, Erwin, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 105)
  - Kulka, Heinrich, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 106)
  - Kunst, Arnold, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 107)
  - Kuratowski, Kazimierz, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 108)
  - Kurth, Ernst, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 109)
  - Kurylowicz, Jerzy, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 110)
  - Kuthmann, Carl, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 111)
  - Laban, Rudolf, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 112)
  - Lachmann, Ludwig Moritz, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 113)
  - Ladenburg, R., Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 114)
  - Ladner, Gerhardt, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 115)
  - Laemmel, Rudolf, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 116)
  - Lameere, Jean, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 117)
  - Lande, Walter, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 118)
  - Landgrebe. Ludwig, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 119)
  - Landsberg, Paul Ludwig, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 120)
  - Landsberger, Franz, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 121)
  - Landshoff, Ludwig, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 122)
  - Landshut, Siegfried, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 123)
  - Langerhans, Heinz, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 124)
  - Langevin, Paul, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 125)
  - Laporte, Jean, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 126)
  - Laqueur, Ernst, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 127)
  - Laqueur, Richard Albrecht, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 128)
  - Larogue, M., Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 129)
  - Lash, Agathe, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 130)
  - Laufenburger, Henry, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 131)
  - Laula, Johann, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 132)
  - Laun, R., Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 133)
  - Lavelle, Louis, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 134)
  - Lavergne, Bernard, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 135)
  - Lavier, Georges, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 136)
  - Lazarus, Paul, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 137)
  - Leblond, Charles, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 138)
  - Lederer, Walther, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 139)
  - Ledermann, Laszlo, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 140)
  - Lehmann, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 141)
  - Lehr, Hanina, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 142)
  - Leibholz, Hermann Gerhard, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 143)
  - Leiper, Henry Smith, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 144)
  - Lenth, Bert, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 145)
  - Lentz, Dietrich von, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 146)
  - Leo, Ulrich Paul Ludwig, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 147)
  - Leon, Paul, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 148)
  - Lessing, Mrs. Theodor, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 149)
  - Leubuscher, Charlotte, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 150)
  - Leupold, Lotte, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 151)
  - Levi, Alessandro, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 152)
  - Levi, Carlo, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 153)
  - Levi, Hermann, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 154)
  - Levi, Isidore, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 155)
  - Levi, Mario, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 156)
  - Levison, Wilhelm, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 157)
  - Levy, Anton, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 158)
  - Levy, Isidore, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 159)
  - Levy, Saul, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 160)
  - Levy, William P., Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 161)
  - Levy-Bruhl, Henri, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 162)
  - Lewy, Ernst, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 163)
  - Leyden, Johan Huizinga, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 164)
  - Lheritier, Michel, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 165)
  - Liebert, Arthur, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 166)
  - Liebeschutz, Hans, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 167)
  - Liebknecht, Robert, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 168)
  - Liefmann, Robert, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 169)
  - Liepmann, Leo, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 170)
  - Lingat, R., Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 171)
  - Linker, Norman, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 172)
  - Lipstein, Kurt, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 173)
  - Liuzzi, Fernando, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 174)
  - Lobl, Rudolf, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 175)
  - Lods, Adolphe, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 176)
  - Loehr, August von, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 177)
  - Loehrich, Rolf, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 178)
  - Loevensohn, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 179)
  - Loewy, Julius, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 180)
  - Lonyay, Simon H., Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 181)
  - Lopez-Rey, Manuel, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 182)
  - Lossky, Nicholas O., Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 183)
  - Lowy, J., Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 184)
  - Luchaire, Julien, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 185)
  - Lukasiewicz, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 186)
  - Lunau, Heinz, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 187)
  - Lurcat, Jean, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 188)
  - Lurcat, Victor, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 189)
  - Lussu, Emilio, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 190)
  - Madaule, Jacques, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 191)